{"data":[{"question":"When Kelly arrived, she learned Edward ___ for almost two hours.","a":"had set off","b":"had gone","c":"had been away","d":"had left","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Away: used to say that someone leaves a place or person, or stays some distance from a place or person","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"Will we go skiing or see a movie at home? \"Which ___ do?\"","a":"would you rather","b":"do you rather","c":"should you rather","d":"will you rather","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Would rather: used to say that you would prefer to do or have","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"That little boy really doesn't want to go to the concert, but he doesn't see how he can ___ it.","a":"get out of","b":"get back from","c":"get off","d":"get away","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Get out of= leave\/escape","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"If no one ___ the phone at home, ring me at work.","a":"replies","b":"returns","c":"receives","d":"answers","answer":"4","explain":"\n- We often use \"Answer phone\"","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"Many readers can't ___ quite well unless they know the exact meaning of each word.","a":"get in","b":"get over","c":"get through","d":"get along","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Get through: to do an amount of work","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"We ___ each other the best of luck in the examination.","a":"wanted","b":"hoped","c":"wished","d":"expected","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Wish: to say that you hope someone will have good luck, a happy life etc","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"___! There's a car rushing toward here!.","a":"Look around","b":"Look out","c":"Look on","d":"Look forward","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Look out = Take care","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"I learned to ___ a car when I was twenty-one.","a":"drive","b":"ride","c":"run","d":"operate","answer":"1","explain":"\n- We often use \"drive a\/the car\"","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"Will somebody go and get Dr. Jefferson? \"She's already been ___\"","a":"sent for","b":"asked for","c":"looked for","d":"called for","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Send for: to ask or order that something be brought or sent to you, especially by writing a letter or by telephone","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"Will you ___ me a favor, please?","a":"make","b":"give","c":"bring","d":"do","answer":"4","explain":"That's right! You chose the correct response.","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"}]}